BEN, EKEMINI SUNDAY

ADDRESS: House 38, 1st Avenue Efab City Estate Life Camp, Abuja Nigeria. PHONE: 08107914902

EMAIL: ekemiben.4@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A graduate of computer science with 5+ years administrative experience, extensive knowledge of customer services and office management. Adapt at resolving guest conflicts, with strong communication skills both written and oral. Highly organised and details oriented, flexible and hardworking with the drive to succeed.

BIODATA

Gender: Male
Marital Status: Single

Religion: Christianity
Date of Birth: 03 October 1992

L. G. A: Uyo

State of Origin: Akwa Ibom Nationality: Nigerian

Language: English and Ibibio/Efik

EDUCATION

Akwa Ibom State Polytechnic, Ikot Osurua, Ikot Ekpene.

Higher National Diploma (HND) in computer science, 2018.

WorldQuant University, U.S.A.

Data Science and Machine learning 2020

PROJECTS

Portfolio and Plumbing website,

Library Management Information System

Financial Accounting Information System

Restaurant Management Information System etc.

EXPERIENCE

- Computer Administrator 2011 2012 at Afix Computers Uyo, Akwa Ibom State.
- Rector's Secretary, 2014 2019 at St. Joseph Major Seminary Ikot Ekpene, Akwa Ibom State.
- Assists clients to solve computer problems in a timely manner, 2011 till date.
- Analyse client-specified problems to develop hardware and software solutions that fulfil operational requirements, 2014 till date.
- ➤ Secondary School Teacher from 2019 2020 at Government Day Secondary School, Jalingo.
- > Software Engineering internship at Tiidelab from July 2021 till date

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Thorough understanding of computer hardware and software, including working in all parts of software development cycle.
- Proficient in HTML, CSS, VB.Net, WordPress, and intermediate in JavaScript, python and django
- Github (version control system) and Trello app for project management.
- Excellent interpersonal skills, such as the ability to make technical information understandable to customers and end users.
- Strong administrative skill.

HOBBIES: I like playing musical instrument (keyboard), football, surfing internet and coding